READY?
YEAH.
OKAY.
HI.
IT'S...
RACHEL...
AND...
PHOEBE'S...
PLEASE...
LEAVE...
WAIT, I-I JUST
SAID, "LEAVE."
YEAH, I KNOW,
BECAUSE YOU HAVE
ALL THE GOOD WORDS.
WHAT DO I GET?
I GET "IT'S,"
"AND"--
OH, I'M SORRY, I HAVE "A."
FORGET IT.
PHOEBE, COME ON.
THAT'S SILLY.
ALL RIGHT,
SO, LET'S SWITCH.
NO, I HAVE ALL
THE GOOD WORDS.
OKAY, FINE, FINE.
WE CAN SWITCH.
OKAY.
HI...
EVERYBODY...
IT'S...
RACHEL...
AND...
PHOEBE'S...
PLEASE... WAIT.
HOW DID YOU DO THAT?
WHAT?
OH... YOU'RE NO
ORDINARY ROOMMATE, ARE YOU?
PH-PHOEBE, COME ON.
CAN WE FINISH THIS LATER?
I WANT TO GO RUNNING
BEFORE IT GETS DARK.
OH! WHY DON'T YOU COME WITH ME?
REALLY?
YEAH.
OH, IT'LL BE FUN.
WE'LL RUN IN THE PARK.
IT'LL BE, LIKE, OUR FIRST
YOU KNOW,
ROOMMATE-BONDING THING.
OKAY, LET'S GO RUNNING.
YEAH...
AND THERE'S REALLY CUTE GUYS.
LET'S RUN TOWARDS THEM!
OKAY.
ALL RIGHT,
WAIT JUST ONE MORE SECOND.
HI. IT'S PHOEBE AND RACHEL'S.
PLEASE LEAVE A MESSAGE. THANKS.
WELL, NOW,
WAIT A MINUTE.
YOU JUST TOOK
ALL THE WORDS.
UH-HUH, YOU'VE MET YOUR MATCH,
RACHEL GREEN.
♪ SO NO ONE TOLD YOU
LIFE WAS GONNA BE THIS WAY ♪
♪ YOUR JOB'S A JOKE,
YOU'RE BROKE ♪
♪ YOUR LOVE LIFE'S D.O.A. ♪
♪ IT'S LIKE YOU'RE ALWAYS
STUCK IN SECOND GEAR ♪
♪ WHEN IT HASN'T BEEN
YOUR DAY, YOUR WEEK ♪
♪ YOUR MONTH,
OR EVEN YOUR YEAR ♪
♪ BUT I'LL BE THERE FOR YOU ♪
♪ 'CAUSE YOU'RE THERE
FOR ME, TOO. ♪
SO, I JUST FINISHED
THIS FASCINATING BOOK.
BY THE YEAR 2030,
THERE'LL BE COMPUTERS
THAT CAN CARRY OUT
THE SAME AMOUNT OF FUNCTIONS
AS AN ACTUAL HUMAN BRAIN.
SO, THEORETICALLY,
YOU COULD DOWNLOAD
YOUR THOUGHTS AND MEMORIES
INTO THIS COMPUTER
AND-AND-AND LIVE FOREVER,
AS A MACHINE.
AND I JUST REALIZED
I CAN SLEEP WITH MY EYES OPEN.
( door opening )
HEY.
HONEY, THAT'S A GREAT IDEA--
NAILING THE BOXES
TO THE FLOOR.
I DIDN'T NAIL THE BOXES
OH, SO YOU CAN MOVE THEM?
YES. YES,
AND WHILE I'M DOING THAT
ROSS HAS A GREAT COMPUTER STORY
FOR YOU.
HEY, EVERYBODY.
UH, I'D LIKE YOU
TO MEET JANINE.
SHE'S-SHE'S GOING TO
BE MY NEW ROOMMATE.
HI.
YEAH, SHE'S GOING
TO LIVE WITH ME!
IT'S NICE TO MEET YOU.
UH, JANINE...
LECROIX, JANINE LECROIX.
I DIDN'T KNOW THAT.
WH-WHAT A PRETTY
LAST NAME.
SO, UH, WH-WHERE
ARE YOU FROM?
AUSTRALIA. I JUST MOVED HERE
A COUPLE OF WEEKS AGO.
FROM THE LAND
DOWN UNDER?
YEAH.
I DIDN'T KNOW
THAT, EITHER.
SO, UH, WHAT, UH,
WHAT DO YOU DO?
I'M A DANCER.
YOU'RE A DANCER?
SHE-SHE'S A DANCER.
Janine:
WELL, I THINK
I'LL GO AND... UNPACK.
OH, HEY, LET ME.
THANKS.
OKAY.
( gasping ecstatically )
JOEY...
YEAH?
DID YOU EVEN INTERVIEW
THIS WOMAN
BEFORE YOU ASKED HER
TO MOVE IN?
OF COURSE I DID.
WHAT EXACTLY
DID YOU ASK HER?
"WHEN CAN YOU MOVE IN?"
THANK YOU FOR BRINGING
HER INTO OUR LIVES.
UNBELIEVABLE.
OH... OH, SO, YOU LIKE HER,
TOO, CHANDLER?
HEY, LOOK AT
ALL THE BOXES.
OH, I CANNOT WAIT
TO ASK HER OUT.
WAIT A MINUTE, JOEY.
JOEY, YOU CAN'T ASK HER OUT.
SHE'S YOUR ROOMMATE.
YOU KNOW, IT'S... IT'LL
BE WAY TOO COMPLICATED.
YEAH, YEAH, MAN,
DON'T DO IT.
I MEAN,
IF YOU DATE HER
THEN-THEN-THEN
I CAN'T DATE HER.
Chandler:
ALL RIGHT,
THINK ABOUT IT.
NOW, REMEMBER WHEN YOU WENT
OUT WITH THAT GIRL, DONNA
AND YOU GUYS BROKE UP?
REMEMBER HOW HORRIBLE IT WAS
WHEN YOU GUYS BUMPED INTO EACH
OTHER AT THE SUPERMARKET?
OH, GOD, YEAH.
NOW, IMAGINE YOU LIVE...
AT THE SUPERMARKET.
OKAY.
NO, NO.
OH. OH.
OH, YOU'RE RIGHT.
I DON'T WANT THAT.
I CAN'T DATE HER.
YEAH, AND YOU BETTER
WATCH THE FLIRTING, TOO
BECAUSE IN SUCH
CLOSE QUARTERS...
IT COULD BE TROUBLE.
WELL, THAT'S GOING
TO BE TOUGH, MON. I MEAN,
IT'S HARD FOR ME TO BE AROUND
AN ATTRACTIVE WOMAN
AND NOT FLIRT.
( chuckles )
WELL, YOU'RE AROUND
ME ALL THE TIME
AND YOU DON'T FLIRT.
YOU A LITTLE SAD
ABOUT THAT, SWEETHEART?
I HAVE TO TIE MY SHOE.
YOU GO AHEAD.
I'LL CATCH UP.
Both:
OKAY.
( panting )
COME ON!
THAT'S NOT RUNNING!
LET'S GO!
YOU GUYS, I'M
TELLING YOU
WHEN SHE RUNS, SHE LOOKS LIKE
A CROSS BETWEEN KERMIT THE FROG
AND THE SIX MILLION DOLLAR MAN.
MONICA HAD SUCH
A CRUSH ON HIM.
( laughing )
YEAH, SHE USED
TO KISS HIS POSTER
EVERY NIGHT
BEFORE SHE WENT TO BED.
OH, I USED TO DO THAT, TOO.
DID YOU ALSO
HAVE HIS ALBUM
IT'S NOT EASY
BEING GREEN?
AW, MON...
( chuckling )
SO, PHOEBE RUNS
WEIRD, HUH?
YEAH, YEAH, AND YOU KNOW WHAT?
AND I KNOW SHE'S GOING
TO WANT TO RUN AGAIN.
I JUST DON'T KNOW HOW
TO GET OUT OF IT.
I MEAN, I LIVE WITH HER.
WHY DON'T YOU JUST BE
STRAIGHT WITH HER?
TELL HER THE TRUTH.
YOU'RE RIGHT.
YOU'RE RIGHT, I SHOULD
JUST TELL HER THE TRUTH.
HEY.
HEY, PHEEBS,
MONICA TRIPPED ME.
I DON'T THINK
I CAN EVER RUN AGAIN, EVER.
WHY?
WHY WOULD
YOU DO THAT?
I DON'T KNOW.
RACHEL, I'M-I'M SORRY
THAT I HURT YOUR ANKLES.
ANKLE.
WE'LL SEE.
OKAY, I AM OFFICIALLY UNPACKED.
THANKS FOR HELPING ME, MAN.
JOE?
( Joey chuckling )
WELL, I GUESS
JOEY WENT HOME.
OH, AND LOOK,
THERE'S STILL ONE BOX
THAT I HAVE TO UNPACK.
( Joey laughing )
I GOTCHA!
( laughing )
OH, MY GOD!
YOU ALMOST GAVE ME
A HEART ATTACK.
BOY, IT WAS SO
HARD NOT TO LAUGH
I'LL TELL YOU.
OH, HEY-HEY...
THE PLACE LOOKS GREAT.
YEAH, NOT BAD, RIGHT?
MONICA'S GOING
TO BE WORKING LATE.
SO, I'M GOING TO MAKE
THIS PLACE SPOTLESS.
YOU KNOW WHAT ELSE
I'M GOING TO DO?
I'M GOING
TO GO DOWNSTAIRS.
I'M GOING TO GET HER
SOME FLOWERS.
NOW, WHO WOULD NOT WANT
TO LIVE WITH ME?
I DON'T.
NO, I WANT TO LIVE
WITH THE SUPER-HOT
AUSTRALIAN DANCER.
OKAY, NOW,
HOW'S THAT GOING NOW?
ARE YOU OKAY
WITH THE NOT-FLIRTING THING?
UH, YEAH, BUT... SO FAR,
YEAH BUT IT'S TOUGH, YOU KNOW?
I GOT ALL THIS-THIS
BUILT-UP FLIRTING ENERGY
AND-AND I DON'T KNOW
HOW TO GET RID OF IT.
HOW YOU DOIN'?
( voice cracking ):
OH, MAN.
SORRY, THERE'S JUST MORE ROOM
OUT HERE.
OH, NO, NO, NO, IT'S-IT'S, UH...
YOU JUST, UH, UH, REMINDED ME
THAT, UH, I HAVE
TO DO MY STRETCHES, TOO, YEAH.
( groaning painfully )
WHY DON'T YOU TRY TO...
( yelping )
WHAT'S WRONG?
UH, UH, NOTHING.
I JUST, UH...
I-I DIDN'T WANT YOU TO TOUCH ME
BECAUSE I'M-I'M
ALL SWEATY
FROM THE WORKOUT.
I'M GOING TO HIT THE SHOWER.
OH, MY GOD!
OH, SORRY ABOUT THAT
STUFF HANGING IN THERE.
IT'S JUST MY THONGS ARE
TOO DELICATE FOR THE DRYER.
OH...
( laughing nervously )
( whimpering )
( exhaling rhythmically )
HI!
( startled yell )
OH, YEAH, UH-HUH,
IT'S ME.
I SAW YOU GRAB
YOUR RUNNING SHOES
THIS MORNING
AND SNEAK OUT.
YOU LIED
SO YOU COULD RUN
BY YOURSELF.
NO, PHOEBE, NO,
I WAS... NO.
YOU KNOW WHAT?
I WAS... I WAS ACTUALLY
JUST CHECKING...
TO SEE... IF I
COULD RUN AND I CAN.
PLEASE, RACHEL,
I AM NOT AN IDIOT.
NO, WAIT, PHOEBE.
WOW... COUPLES
WHO LIVE TOGETHER DO START
TO LOOK ALIKE.
SO... MON-DLER...
UH...
WHAT, UH... WH...
WHAT YOU DOING?
WHAT DOES IT LOOK LIKE?
I AM CLEANING.
DID YOU GET MONICA'S
AUTHORIZATION
TO MOVE ALL
OF HER STUFF?
"AUTHORIZATION"--
I DON'T NEED THAT.
I'M GONNA
PUT EVERYTHING BACK.
PUT IT BACK EXACTLY
WHERE YOU FOUND IT?
YES, I'M GOING TO PUT IT BACK
"EXACTLY" WHERE I FOUND IT.
OKAY, FIRST OF ALL, THAT
ATTITUDE IS NOT HELPING.
OKAY, SHE IS NOT
GOING TO CARE
IF I PUT HER STUFF BACK
IN THE SAME STUPID PLACE.
OH, HELLO?
DID YOU JUST MEET MONICA?
SHE'S GOING TO RECOGNIZE
THAT I DID A NICE THING
AND-AND APPRECIATE IT.
HUH.
YOU KNOW, ACTUALLY
THIS WILL WORK OUT WELL
BECAUSE WHEN YOU HAVE
TO MOVE BACK IN WITH JOEY
JOEY'S HOT NEW ROOMMATE
CAN COME LIVE WITH ME.
I SEE. I SEE.
Y-Y-YOU'RE TRYING
TO FREAK ME OUT.
LOOK, CHANDLER, MONICA
IS REALLY WEIRD
ABOUT THIS KIND OF
STUFF, ALL RIGHT?
BELIEVE ME, I LIVED
WITH HER FOR 16 YEARS.
SHE IS GOING TO FREAK OUT.
OH, MY GOD,
SHE'S GOING TO SIT ON YOU.
NO, SHE'S NOT, OKAY?
YOU KNOW,
I'LL PROVE IT TO YOU.
I'M GOING
TO CALL HER RIGHT NOW.
PHONE'S DONE.
( chuckles sarcastically )
HEY, MON,
HOW'S IT GOING?
Monica:
Terrible.
I TELL YOU, IF-IF-IF I WANT
SOMETHING DONE RIGHT
I HAVE TO DO IT MYSELF.
Other people just wreck stuff.
I REALLY THINK
I MIGHT KILL SOMEONE TONIGHT.
OH, COME ON, COME ON,
IT CAN'T BE THAT BAD.
IT'S WORSE.
THE ONLY THING
GETTING ME THROUGH IS
KNOWING I'M GONNA
BE SEEING YOU SOON.
I think I might even try
to get out of here early.
NO, NO, NO, NO, NO, NO, NO.
NO, IT SOUNDS LIKE
THEY REALLY NEED YOU DOWN THERE.
AREN'T YOU JUST
HANGING OUT WITH ROSS?
IT'S ALL GOOD.
OKAY, BYE-BYE, MON.
SH-SHE'S GOING TO KILL ME.
YOU KNOW, THE PHONE WAS FACING
THE OTHER WAY...
AND THAT GOES
BACK UP THERE.
YOU KNOW WHAT WE SHOULD DO?
WE SHOULD START WITH
THE BIG STUFF,
YOU KNOW?
THAT'LL BE THE EASIEST.
SO, UH, LET'S START
WITH THE COUCH.
I GOT IT.
YEAH, THAT-THAT
DOESN'T LOOK RIGHT.
WHAT ARE YOU TALKING ABOUT?
THE COUCH IS PERFECTLY IN LINE
WITH THE CARPET
AND THEN I COULD JUST
WALK OVER HERE
AND CASUALLY JUST PUT
MY FEET RIGHT UP ON...
OKAY, HERE'S WHAT WE DO--
WE JUST, UH,
MOVE THE COUCH CLOSER
TO THE COFFEE TABLE.
WHOA, YEAH, BUT THEN
THE BACK OF THE COUCH
WON'T LINE UP WITH
THE BACK OF THE CARPET.
OKAY, WELL, HERE--
WE'LL JUST, UH...
WE'LL MOVE THE COFFEE TABLE
CLOSER TO THE COUCH.
NO, WHOA! WHOA!
BUT THEN THE COFFEE TABLE
WON'T BE CENTERED
IN THE SEATING AREA.
YES, BUT THE COFFEE TABLE
DOESN'T HAVE TO...
( blubbering )
ROSS!
ALL RIGHT, LOOK,
WHAT AM I GOING TO DO?
I'M NOT FLIRTING, BUT STILL,
I'M-I'M DRAWING HER TO ME
LIKE-LIKE-LIKE
A MOTH TO A FLAME!
WHAT THE HELL'S
GOING ON OVER HERE?!
MONICA'S GOING TO KILL YOU.
LOOK, I NEED YOUR HELP, OKAY?
I HAVE TO DO SOMETHING
TO-TO REPEL THIS WOMAN.
WAIT A MINUTE, WAIT A MINUTE.
YOU GUYS REPEL WOMEN
ALL THE TIME!
HEY, I'VE BEEN MARRIED
THREE TIMES.
NO, NO, NO, NO, NO!
I'VE SEEN IT HAPPEN.
YOU GET A RAPPORT GOING
WITH A WOMAN,
BUT SOMEHOW YOU MANAGE
TO KILL IT.
WHAT'S YOUR SECRET?
LOOK, WE DO NOT
REPEL WOMEN, OKAY?
THAT IS COMPLETELY UNTRUE.
UH, YES, WE DO, MY MAN.
REMEMBER WHEN WE WERE
BACK IN COLLEGE
AND WE WENT
TO THAT SPRING DANCE
AND YOU WALKED RIGHT UP
TO THAT GIRL YOU LIKED
AND YOU COULD NOT
STOP TALKING ABOUT
THE IRISH
POTATO FAMINE?
WELL, WHAT ABOUT YOU?
YOU WEREN'T SO, YOU KNOW,
HOT IN COLLEGE, EITHER.
AFTER EVERYTHING HE SAID,
HE'D GO "BA-DUM-BUMP. CHSSH."
YEAH, MONICA DOESN'T
LIKE THAT, EITHER.
MAYBE I SHOULD STOP
DOING THAT.
WELL, YOU KNOW WHAT?
GIRLS DON'T LIKE IT
WHEN I START TALKING
ABOUT SCIENCE.
THAT'S NOT SPECIFIC
TO GIRLS.
THIS IS GREAT,
THIS IS GREAT!
WHAT-WHAT ELSE,
WHAT ELSE?
UH... OH, THEY DON'T LIKE IT
WHEN YOU CORRECT THEIR GRAMMAR.
AND THEY DON'T LIKE IT
WHEN YOU EXPLAIN WHY
YOUR JOKES ARE FUNNY.
YOU KNOW, THEY DON'T LIKE IT
WHEN YOU KEEP ASKING THEM
IF THEY LIKE YOU.
MAN, I AM SO LUCKY
I HAVE MONICA.
I'M NEVER GOING TO
FIND LOVE AGAIN.
HEY.
PHOEBE, CAN I TALK TO YOU
FOR A SECOND?
SURE.
OKAY, UM, I...
ALL RIGHT, PHOEBE, LOOK--
I JUST WANTED TO SAY
THAT I'M SORRY, OKAY?
I HANDLED THE SITUATION
HORRIBLY
AND-AND I SHOULD NOT HAVE LIED
TO YOU.
SO, WHAT SHOULD YOU HAVE DONE?
WELL, I-I SHOULD HAVE
TOLD YOU THE TRUTH.
UH-HUH...
WHICH IS?
WELL, YOU KNOW...
THE REASON THAT I DIDN'T WANT
TO GO RUNNING WITH YOU IS
BECAUSE, UH, WELL, YOU KNOW,
THE WAY THAT YOU RUN
IS JUST A LITTLE...
SO?
WELL, IT'S EMBARRASSING.
PEOPLE WERE LOOKING AT US
LIKE WE WERE CRAZY.
WHY DO YOU CARE?
BECAUSE THEY'RE PEOPLE.
BUT PEOPLE THAT YOU DON'T KNOW
AND WILL NEVER SEE AGAIN.
YES, BUT STILL, THEY ARE
PEOPLE...
WITH EYES.
WELL, I DIDN'T GET EMBARRASSED
RUNNING NEXT TO MISS...
( panting )
BUT, OH, OKAY.
NO, NO, I CAN SEE
WHY RUNNING WITH ME
WOULD BE EMBARRASSING TO YOU.
YEAH, OKAY.
YOU'RE UPTIGHT.
WH...!
I... LIS...
I AM NOT UPTIGHT...
( laughing ):
NO...
LISTEN, I AM NOT...
UPTIGHT, MAN.
THAT'S OKAY, RACHEL.
I'M NOT JUDGING YOU.
THAT'S JUST WHO YOU ARE.
ME, I'M MORE FREE,
YOU KNOW?
I RUN LIKE I DID
WHEN I WAS A KID
BECAUSE IT'S THE ONLY WAY
IT'S FUN, YOU KNOW?
I MEAN, DIDN'T YOU EVER
RUN SO FAST
YOU THOUGHT YOUR LEGS
WERE GOING TO FALL OFF?
YOU KNOW, LIKE WHEN YOU WERE
RUNNING TOWARD THE SWINGS
OR-OR RUNNING AWAY
FROM SATAN?
THE NEIGHBORS' DOG.
OH.
OKAY, IS THIS LAMP
IN THE RIGHT PLACE?
WHO CARES? I REPEL WOMEN.
NO, NO, NO, NO, NO, NO!
YOU CAN'T COME IN HERE.
R-R-ROSS IS NAKED!
WHAT?!
I COULDN'T SAY
THAT I WAS NAKED
BECAUSE SHE'S ALLOWED
TO SEE ME NAKED.
WHY DOES ANYONE
HAVE TO BE NAKED?
WHY IS ROSS NAKED?
I... I HAD TO...
SHOW CHANDLER SOMETHING.
NAKED?
YEAH, I-I, UH...
I GUESS I HAVE A, UH...
A GUY PROBLEM.
IS IT THE SAME THING
THAT CHANDLER HAD?
LOOK, UH, JUST-JUST
COME BACK LATER.
WE'LL GET EVERYTHING
SQUARED AWAY
AND YOU CAN COME BACK LATER.
OKAY.
HEY, LISTEN, THERE'S STILL SOME
OF CHANDLER'S MEDICINE LEFT
UNDER THE SINK IN
THE BATHROOM. BYE.
BYE-BYE.
THANK GOD.
DUDE, WHAT'D YOU HAVE?
LOOK, WE HAVE NO TIME, OKAY?
WE MUST FOCUS.
WE GOT TO GET EVERYTHING BACK
INTO ITS
ORIGINAL PLACE.
THE PHOTO ALBUM.
THERE WERE MILLIONS OF
PICTURES OF THE APARTMENT
IN THE PHOTO ALBUM.
WE JUST GO THROUGH IT AND MATCH
EVERYTHING TO THE PICTURES.
THAT'S PERFECT.
THAT'S BRILLIANT.
SO, REALLY,
WHAT'D YOU HAVE?
HEY, JOEY, I GOT
SOME BEER FOR YOU.
UH, DON'T-DON'T YOU MEAN,
"FOR WHOM"?
SURE.
LISTEN, I WAS GOING TO ORDER
SOME PIZZA.
YOU WANT TO SHARE ONE?
PIZZA? HA! IT'S NOT LIKE
I'VE NEVER HAD THAT BEFORE.
BA-DUM-BUMP. CHSSH.
IS THERE SOMETHING WRONG?
ALL RIGHT, ALL RIGHT.
LET'S JUST GET THIS OUT
IN THE OPEN, OKAY?
YOU'RE HOT.
I'M LOVABLE.
CLEARLY, THERE'S A VIBE
GOING ON BETWEEN US
BUT WE'RE ROOMMATES
AND IT'S A HUGE MISTAKE FOR US
TO CONTINUE DOWN THIS ROAD.
JOEY...
NO, NO, NO, I'M TELLING YOU.
IMAGINE YOURSELF
LIVING IN A SUPERMARKET
AND YOU WILL
UNDERSTAND.
OKAY, SO THE QUESTION IS,
WHAT DO WE DO?
WELL, I DON'T THINK
THERE IS ANYTHING TO DO.
I MEAN, I THINK
YOU'RE REALLY SWEET
BUT I'M JUST NOT INTERESTED
IN YOU LIKE THAT.
OH!
NO, I MEAN...
( sighing ):
YOU'RE A REALLY NICE GUY
AND I'M HAPPY TO BE
YOUR ROOMMATE
AND YOUR FRIEND.
I'M JUST...
YOU KNOW, I JUST DON'T
FEEL THAT WAY ABOUT YOU.
OH... I SEE WHAT HAPPENED.
( laughing )
IT'S BECAUSE I WAS TRYING
TO REPEL YOU, RIGHT?
BELIEVE ME, YOU'D FEEL A LOT
DIFFERENT IF I TURNED IT ON.
I DON'T THINK SO.
OH, I DO.
HOW YOU DOIN'?
I'M OKAY.
WHAT?
OH, DEAR GOD!
( panting )
( both screaming )
HEY!
PHEEBS!
OH, HONEY, I'M SO SORRY.
YOU WERE RIGHT--
THIS FEELS GREAT!
SEE? AND YOU DON'T CARE
IF PEOPLE ARE STARING.
IT'S JUST FOR A SECOND,
'CAUSE THEN YOU'RE GONE!
GONE!
I MEAN, IT'S AMAZING, PHEEBS!
I FEEL SO FREE,
AND SO GRACEFUL...
AAH!
HEY! LOOK OUT FOR THE HORSE.
SORRY.
IS IT OKAY FOR ME
TO COME IN NOW?
UH-HUH.
WHY IS EVERYTHING DIFFERENT?
BYE.
NO, I DON'T SEE
ANYTHING DIFFERENT
OTHER THAN THE FACT THAT THE
ROOM GOT SO MUCH BRIGHTER
WHEN YOU CAME INTO IT.
( forced laugh )
WELL, THE END TABLE IS WRONG
AND THE COUCH LOOKS BIZARRE
AND DON'T EVEN GET ME STARTED
ON THE REFRIGERATOR MAGNETS.
OKAY, LOOK, DON'T...
DON'T BE MAD, OKAY?
BUT AFTER I UNPACKED THE BOXES
I WANTED TO DO SOMETHING NICE
FOR YOU
SO I-I-I CLEANED THE APARTMENT.
SO I MOVED EVERYTHING AROUND
AND THEN I-I FORGOT WHERE IT...
WHERE IT WENT BACK.
AND I'M SORRY. I'M VERY SORRY,
I'M SORRY, I'M SORRY.
THAT'S OKAY.
CHANDLER, ARE YOU AFRAID OF ME
OR SOMETHING?
DO YOU WANT ME TO BE
AFRAID OF YOU?
OF COURSE NOT.
OH, MY GOSH, CHANDLER,
WHAT YOU DID--
IT'S-IT'S SUCH A WONDERFUL THING
AND I REALLY APPRECIATE IT.
I KNOW I HAVE
THIS WEIRD THING
WHERE I WANT EVERYTHING
TO BE IN THE PERFECT PLACE
BUT I WOULD NEVER EXPECT YOU
TO WORRY ABOUT THAT.
REALLY?
OF COURSE.
OH, WELL, YOU'RE THE BEST.
YOU COME HERE TO ME.
ALL RIGHT, HOLD ON, OKAY?
FIRST THINGS FIRST.
OKAY, NOW...
DID ROSS SIT ANYWHERE
WHILE HE WAS NAKED?
SO IT'S SAID THAT
BY THE YEAR 2030
THERE'LL BE COMPUTERS
THAT CAN CARRY OUT
THE SAME NUMBER OF FUNCTIONS
AS AN ACTUAL HUMAN BRAIN.
SO THEORETICALLY,
YOU CAN DOWNLOAD
YOUR THOUGHTS
AND YOUR MEMORIES
INTO THIS COMPUTER...
AND LIVE FOREVER
AS A MACHINE!
UH, SO, JANINE,
YOU-YOU-YOU KNOW WHAT...
YOU KNOW WHAT WE'RE
DOING RIGHT NOW?
YOU AND I, WE'RE-WE'RE
INTERFACING.
YEAH.
I GOT TO GO.
BA-DUM-BUMP. CHSSH.